<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Runar</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_layouts">Runic Draws</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_library">Library</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_favourites">Favourites</string>
    <string name="bottom_nav_menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="generator">Generator</string>

    <string name="pattern_generator">Pattern generator</string>
    <string name="run_pattern">Rune pattern</string>
    <string name="run_patterns">Rune patterns</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="formula">Runic Formula</string>
    <string name="stav">Runic Staves</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">Coming soon</string>
    <string name="runes_selection">Runes selection</string>
    <string name="runes_collect_formula">Select 1 to 3 runes and collect your rune draw</string>
    <string name="runes_random">Choose random runes</string>
    <string name="generator_fog">Generator is covered in mist</string>
    <string name="generator_fog_desc">The wisdom of the generator is available to premium-subscribers</string>

    <string name="runes_generate">Generate</string>


    <string name="layout1">RUNE OF THE DAY</string>
    <string name="layout2">2 RUNES</string>
    <string name="layout3">NORNS</string>
    <string name="layout4">BRIEF PROPHECY</string>
    <string name="layout5">THOR\'S HAMMER</string>
    <string name="layout6">CROSS</string>
    <string name="layout7">CROSS OF ELEMENTS</string>
    <string name="layout8">CELTIC CROSS</string>
    <string name="layout_upper_banner_description">Create your runic pattern by selecting a few runes</string>
    <string name="rune_layouts">Rune layouts</string>

    <string name="layout_description_checkbox">Do not show again</string>
    <string name="layout_description_button">Start Runic Draw</string>

    <string name="layout_init_button_text1">Pull Out a Rune</string>
    <string name="layout_init_button_text2">Get Interpretation</string>

    <string name="layout_init_button_text4">Processing…</string>
    <string name="layout_init_processing">Ravendark Guitars</string>

    <string name="layout_description_product">Products description</string>
    <string name="layout_go_to_site">Check the website</string>

    <string name="info_popup_button_text">Ок</string>

    <string name="description_runic_draws_popup">Do you really want to stop\nRunic Draw?</string>
    <string name="description_generator_popup">Do you really want to stop\nGenerator?</string>
    <string name="description_popup_button1">No</string>
    <string name="description_popup_button2">Yes</string>
    <string name="layout_interpretation_checkbox">Save this draw</string>
    <string name="layout_interpretation_button">Finish</string>
    <string name="layout_interpretation_ausf">Luckiness</string>

    <string name="text_calculation_helper">The fame and popularity of this divination </string>

    <string name="settings_layout">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_language">Language</string>
    <string name="settings_language_rus" translatable="false">Русский</string>
    <string name="settings_language_en" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="music_txt">Music</string>
    <string name="onboarding_txt">Show onboard page</string>
    <string name="rate_app_txt">Rate the application</string>
    <string name="about_app_txt">About</string>
    <string name="developer_options_title">Developer Options</string>
    <string name="about_txt">Application version 0.25\n\nRunar is an app for reading Scandinavian runes and studying mythology and fairy tales. Contains 8 types of rune layouts and runes interpretation. In the Library section you can read Scandinavian sagas and fairy tales.\n\nWith the permission of the copyright holders, the following musical compositions are used in the application:\n- Lyod (tracks \"Black rook\", \"My mother told\"), https://lyod1.bandcamp.com/releases \n- Danheim (tracks \"Runar\", \"Kala\"), https://danheimmusic.com</string>
    <string name="library_top_bar_header">Library</string>
    <string name="fav_dialog_text">Do you really want to delete your favorite layouts?</string>

    <string name="library_bar_fav">Favourites</string>
    <string name="fav_checkbox_text">Select all</string>

    <string name="about_url1">https://lyod1.bandcamp.com/releases</string>
    <string name="about_url2">https://danheimmusic.com/license-music/</string>

    <string name="group1">Lyod</string>
    <string name="group2">Danheim</string>
    <string name="track1_1">Black rook</string>
    <string name="track1_2">My mother told</string>
    <string name="track2_1">Kala</string>
    <string name="track2_2">Runar</string>

    <string name="helper_text">Tap on the runic draw,\n and learn the details about the runes</string>

    <string name="onboard_skip">Skip</string>

    <string name="onboard_begin">Start</string>
    <string name="onboard_next">Next</string>

    <string name="onboard_header1">What the app is about</string>
    <string name="onboard_text1">Get answers to exciting questions with the help of runes</string>
    <string name="onboard_header2">How to read runes</string>
    <string name="onboard_text2">Choose one of the eight divinations and see the interpretation of your fate</string>
    <string name="onboard_header3">Interpretation</string>
    <string name="onboard_text3">See the interpretation of each divination with the luckiness level</string>
    <string name="onboard_header4">Favourites</string>
    <string name="onboard_text4">Save your favourite interpretations and meanings of runes to your Favourites</string>
    <string name="onboard_header5">Generator</string>
    <string name="onboard_text5">Forge your own destiny, collect a rune pattern and choose a background for it</string>
    <string name="onboard_header6">Library</string>
    <string name="onboard_text6">Go to the Library of Knowledge, learn fairy tales, mythology and the history of runes</string>

    <string name="sacr_button_header">Принести жертву богам</string>
    <string name="sacr_button_text">Активация и поддержка новых фичей, и креативных идей.</string>
    <string name="sacr_header_1">Жертва Богам</string>
    <string name="sacr_header_2">Свершилось</string>
    <string name="sacr_sub_header">Принести в жертву</string>
    <string name="sacr_text">Жертва Богам повышает ваш уровень удачи и увеличивает возможность благоприятного исхода ваших дел.\n\nДелая жертву Богам, сфокусируйте свой разум на проблеме или деяниях своих. И Боги обратят на вас свой взор, одаряя вас внутренней силой и упорством на пути к вашей цели.\nПосле чего сама Судьба проведёт вас за руку по тропе благополучия.</string>
    <string name="sacr_item_1">Бить челом</string>
    <string name="sacr_item_2">Кофе</string>
    <string name="sacr_item_3">Эль</string>
    <string name="sacr_button2_price">$2</string>
    <string name="sacr_button3_price">$5</string>
    <string name="sacr_hint_text">You’ll be charged</string>
    <string name="sacr_google_pay_text">You’ll be taken to a thank you page after the payment. By continuing, you agree to the terms and privacy police.</string>
    <string name="sacr_last_button_text">Продолжить путь</string>
    <string name="sacr_result_text">Жертва принесена, и Боги обратили на тебя свой взор. Теперь продолжи свой путь!</string>

    <string name="generatorBackground">Select background</string>
    <string name="text_magic_happens">Magic happens</string>
    <string name="fate_created">Template is creating … </string>
    <string name="do_not_despair">Do not despair if today the runes do not tell you fate, but then you will need to choose .....</string>
    <string name="runic_pattern">Runic pattern</string>
    <string name="text_for_viking">Next, choose a background for it, viking</string>
    <string name="pattern_created">Pattern created</string>
    <string name="new_option">See more</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="background_generator">To get started, choose your favorite picture</string>
    <string name="image_saved">Runic pattern is saved</string>
    <string name="permission_denied">Storage access denied</string>

    <string name="library_tab_books">Books</string>
    <string name="library_tab_audio">Audio</string>

    <string name="push_general_notification">Just open Runar and find out what’s the rune of the day</string>
    <string name="push_general_notification_channel_name">Reminders</string>
    <string name="heading" translatable="false">Heading</string>
    <string name="some_description" translatable="false">Some Description</string>
    <string name="luck_is_close">A little more, and you\'ll catch up the luck!</string>
    <string name="today_your_day">Hey, it\'s your lucky day!</string>
    <string name="lucky">The gods favor you!</string>
    <string name="luck_next_time">Better luck next time!</string>

    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="internet_conn_error">Please check your network connection and try again</string>
    <string name="internet_conn_error1">No internet connection</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="subsription">Subscription</string>
    //RunarPremium Fragment Strings
    <string name="runar_premium">Runar premium</string>
    <string name="get_a_full_access">Get a full access to Runar</string>
    <string name="all_runic_draws">All runic draws</string>
    <string name="all_runes_description">All runes description</string>
    <string name="audio_library">Audio library</string>
    <string name="runic_patterns_generator">Runic patterns generator</string>
    <string name="choose_payment_plan">Choose a payment plan</string>
    <string name="pay">Pay the plan</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title"> Privacy Policy </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title_2">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_title">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="conditions">Conditions</string>
    <string name="last_update">Last updated July 27, 2022</string>
    <string name="conditions_notifications">This privacy notice for Runar App (\&quot;Company\&quot;, \&quot;we\&quot;, \&quot;us\&quot;, or \&quot;our\&quot;), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share ("process") your information when you use our Application ("The App"), such as when you:\n- Download and use our mobile application (Runar App), or any other application of ours (Services) that links to this privacy notice\n- Engage with us in other related ways, including any sales, marketing, or events.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_predesc">Please read these terms and conditions carefully before using Our Service (Runar App).</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_definitions">Definitions</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_definitions">For the purposes of these Terms and Conditions:
\&quot;Application\&quot; means the software program provided by the Runar App Team downloaded by You on any electronic device, named Runar App.\n
\&quot;Application Store\&quot; means the digital distribution service operated and developed by Apple Inc. (Apple App Store) or Google Inc. (Google Play Store) in which the Application has been downloaded.\n
\&quot;Runar App Team\&quot; (referred to as either \&quot;the Company\&quot;, \&quot;We\&quot;, \&quot;Us\&quot; or \&quot;Our\&quot; in this Agreement) refers to Runar App Team.\n
\&quot;Country\&quot; refers to Poland.\n
\&quot;Content\&quot; refers to content such as text, images, or other information that can be posted, uploaded, linked to or otherwise made available by You, regardless of the form of that content.\n
\&quot;Device\&quot; means any device that can access the Runar App such as a computer, a cell phone or a digital tablet.\n
\&quot;Feedback\&quot; means feedback, innovations or suggestions sent by You regarding the attributes, performance or features of our Service.\n
\&quot;Service\&quot; refers to the https://runar.app/.\n
\&quot;Third-party Social Media Service\&quot; means any services or content (including data, information, products or services) provided by a third-party that may be displayed, included or made available by the Service.\n
    \&quot;Website\&quot; refers to https://runar.app/\n
        \&quot;You\&quot; means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_acknowledgment">Acknowledgment</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_acknowledgment">These are the Terms and Conditions governing the use of this Service and the agreement that operates between You and the Company. These Terms and Conditions set out the rights and obligations of all users regarding the use of the Service.
Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on Your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.
By accessing or using the Service You agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If You disagree with any part of these Terms and Conditions then You may not access the Service.
Your access to and use of the Service is also conditioned on Your acceptance of and compliance with the Privacy Policy of the Company. Our Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your personal information when You use the Application or the Website and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You. Please read Our Privacy Policy carefully before using Our Service.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_copyright_policy">Copyright Policy</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_copyright_policy">We respect the intellectual property rights of others. It is Our policy to respond to any claim that Content posted on the Service infringes a copyright or other intellectual property infringement of any person.
If You are a copyright owner, or authorized on behalf of one, and You believe that the copyrighted work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement that is taking place through the Service, You must submit Your notice in writing to the attention of our copyright agent via email (runarapp@gmail.com) and include in Your notice a detailed description of the alleged infringement.
You may be held accountable for damages (including costs and attorneys fees) for misrepresenting that any Content is infringing Your copyright.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_intellectual_property">Intellectual Property</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_intellectual_property">The Runar and its original content (excluding Content provided by You or other users), features and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of the Company and its licensors.
The Runar app is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the Country and foreign countries.
Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service without the prior written consent of the Company.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_your_feedback_to_us">Your Feedback to Us</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_your_feedback_to_us">You assign all rights, title and interest in any Feedback You provide the Company. If for any reason such assignment is ineffective, You agree to grant the Company a non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty free, worldwide right and license to use, reproduce, disclose, sub-license, distribute, modify and exploit such Feedback without restriction.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_links_to_other_websites">Links to Other Websites</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_links_to_other_websites">Our Service may contain links to third-party websites or services that are not owned or controlled by the Company.
The Company has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party websites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that the Company shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services.
We strongly advise You to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party websites or services that You visit.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_governing_law">Governing Law</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_governing_law">The laws of the Country, excluding its conflicts of law rules, shall govern this Terms and Your use of the Service. Your use of the Application may also be subject to other local, state, national, or international laws.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_disputes_resolution">Disputes Resolution</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_disputes_resolution">If You have any concern or dispute about the Service, You agree to first try to resolve the dispute informally by contacting the Company.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_for_european_union">For European Union (EU) Users</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_for_european_union">If You are a European Union consumer, you will benefit from any mandatory provisions of the law of the country in which you are resident in.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_the_united_states">The United States Legal Compliance</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_the_united_states">You represent and warrant that (i) You are not located in a country that is subject to the United States government embargo, or that has been designated by the United States government as a "terrorist supporting" country, and (ii) You are not listed on any United States government list of prohibited or restricted parties.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_severability">Severability</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_severability">If any provision of these Terms is held to be unenforceable or invalid, such provision will be changed and interpreted to accomplish the objectives of such provision to the greatest extent possible under applicable law and the remaining provisions will continue in full force and effect.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_changes">Changes to These Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_changes">We reserve the right, at Our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material We will make reasonable efforts to provide at least 30 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at Our sole discretion.
By continuing to access or use Our Service after those revisions become effective, You agree to be bound by the revised terms. If You do not agree to the new terms, in whole or in part, please stop using the website and the Service.</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_desc_contact_us">If you have any questions about these Terms and Conditions, You can contact us:
By visiting this page on our website: https://runar.app/
By sending us an email: runarapp@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="personal_information">1. Personal information you disclose to us.</string>
    <string name="content_personal_information_1">We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products, when you participate in activities on the App, or otherwise when you contact us.\n The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the App, the choices you make, and the products and features you use.\n If you use our application(s), we also may collect the following information if you choose to provide us with access or permission:</string>
    <string name="content_personal_information_2">- Geolocation Information. We may request access or permission to track location-based information from your mobile\n- Device type, either continuously or while you are using our mobile application(s), to provide certain location-based \n- Services. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device\'s settings.\n This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our application(s), for troubleshooting, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.\n All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.</string>
    <string name="app_do_not">Runar App DO NOT:</string>
    <string name="app_do_not_content">- Handle non-public phonebook or contact information\n- Contain anti-virus or security functionality, such as anti-virus, anti-malware, or security-related features\n- Targets children\n- Collects or links persistent device identifiers (e.g., IMEI, IMSI, SIM Serial #, etc.)\n- Use ads</string>
    <string name="information_process">2. Information process</string>
    <string name="information_process_content">We process your personal information for a variety of reasons, depending on how you interact with our Services, including:- To save or protect an individual\'s vital interest. We may process your information when necessary to save or protect an individual\'s vital interest, such as to prevent harm.</string>
    <string name="storing_of_information">3. Strong of information</string>
    <string name="storing_of_information_content_1">For storing users\' data we use secure Google Firebase. Thus the security of your data is guaranteed by Google. We are also constantly working on a variety of additional functions that can be used for secure storing your data.</string>
    <string name="storing_of_information_content_2">We store information that you provide to our Services for 6 mouths, so that these Services were able to provide their services to you. If you delete your account, we will also remove your information. But please keep in mind: (1) removing this information from our servers and from storage may be delayed; (2) we can save this information if it is necessary for the rule of law, disputes resolution, or for the fulfillment of the conditions of our agreements.</string>
    <string name="storing_of_information_content_3">To ensure the performance of our Services and providing you with our services, we store, process and transmit information at points located around the world (including outside of your country). Also, the information can be stored on the devices you use to access our Services.</string>
    <string name="legal_base">4. Legal base</string>
    <string name="legal_base_content_2">- Legal Obligations. We may process your information where we believe it is necessary for compliance with our legal obligations, such as to cooperate with a law enforcement body or regulatory agency, exercise or defend our legal rights, or disclose your information as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.</string>
    <string name="legal_base_content_1">The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and UK GDPR require us to explain the valid legal bases we rely on in order to process your personal information. As such, we may rely on the following legal bases to process your personal information:\n\n- Consent. We may process your information if you have given us permission (i.e., consent) to use your personal information for a specific purpose. You can withdraw your consent at any time.</string>
    <string name="sharing_of_personal">5. Sharing of personal information</string>
    <string name="sharing_of_personal_content">We may need to share your personal information in the following situations:\n\n- Business Transfers. We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.</string>
    <string name="term_of_keeping">6. Term of keeping your information</string>
    <string name="term_of_keeping_content">We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us keeping your personal information for longer than 6 months.\n\nWhen we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.</string>
    <string name="third_party">7. Third-party websites</string>
    <string name="third_party_content_1">The App may link to third-party websites, online services, or mobile applications and/or contain advertisements from third parties that are not affiliated with us and which may link to other websites, services, or applications. Accordingly, we do not make any guarantee regarding any such third parties, and we will not be liable for any loss or damage caused by the use of such third-party websites, services, or applications. The inclusion of a link towards a third-party website, service, or application does not imply an endorsement by us. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of data you provide to any third parties.</string>
    <string name="third_party_content_2">Any data collected by third parties is not covered by this privacy notice. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other websites, services, or applications that may be linked to or from the Services.\n\nYou should review the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond to your questions.</string>
    <string name="controls_for">8. Controls for do-not-track features</string>
    <string name="controls_for_content">Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track ("DNT") feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage no uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice.</string>
    <string name="notice_updates">9. Notice updates</string>
    <string name="notice_updates_content">We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated "Revised" date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.</string>
    <string name="contact_information">10. Contact information</string>
    <string name="contact_information_content">If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at runarapp@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="review_update_delete">11. Review, update, or delete the data we collect</string>
    <string name="review_update_delete_content">Based on the applicable laws of your country, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it.</string>

    <string name="d">days</string>
    <string name="h">hours</string>
    <string name="m">minutes</string>
    <string name="s">seconds</string>

    <string name="oh_sorry">Oh, what a pity!</string>
    <string name="rune_powers_not_enough">The Runic power is not strong enough. Recharging will take (%s)</string>

    <string name="watch_ad">Watch an ad</string>
    <string name="purchase_subs">Subscribe</string>

    
</resources>